var jsonColor = `{
  "id": 102,
  "title": "Color",
  "clues": [{
      "id": 3000,
      "answer": "Self colored",
      "question": "A horse that has a main and tail that are the same color as the body",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3001,
      "answer": "Skewbald",
      "question": "A term used to describe a paint or pinto horse that has white on any base coat color other than black",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3002,
      "answer": "Bay",
      "question": "A horse with a brown body, black manes and tails, and points on the legs, faces, and ears",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3003,
      "answer": "Dun",
      "question": "Horses of this type can be a variety of shades, but usually have a dorsal stripe",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3004,
      "answer": "Palomino",
      "question": "A horse with a golden coat and creamy white manes and tails",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3005,
      "answer": "Black",
      "question": "A horse with a black eyes, skin, hooves with black points",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3006,
      "answer": "Bay",
      "question": "The base coat color of the red roan",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3007,
      "answer": "Roan",
      "question": "Term for the coat color in which white hairs and colored hairs are an even mixture and do not change over time",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3008,
      "answer": "Pink",
      "question": "The skin color of a true white horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3009,
      "answer": "Dorsal stripe",
      "question": "The name of the marking down the center of the back of a dun colored horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3010,
      "answer": "Rust",
      "question": "A perlino colored horse has this color points",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3011,
      "answer": "Palomino",
      "question": "The color horse you get when you cross a chestnut colored horse and a cremello colored horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3012,
      "answer": "Melanin",
      "question": "This pigment controls the color of the horses skin and hair",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3013,
      "answer": "Blue roan",
      "question": "The roan-colored horse in which black the base color",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3014,
      "answer": "Chestnut",
      "question": "Cremello is a double dilution of this color",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3015,
      "answer": "Flaxen",
      "question": "The term for the mane and tail of the chestnut colored horse being very light in color",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3016,
      "answer": "Bay",
      "question": "Perlino is a result of the double dilution of this color",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3017,
      "answer": "Chestnut",
      "question": "The base coat color of the strawberry roan colored horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3018,
      "answer": "Chestnut",
      "question": "This color hair mixes with white hairs in a strawberry roan",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3019,
      "answer": "5",
      "question": "The number of basic horse coat colors",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3020,
      "answer": "Dilution",
      "question": "A lessening of the intensity of the basic color hair",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3021,
      "answer": "Star",
      "question": "A common horse marking. It is white hair found in a small area on the horseâ€™s forehead area",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 3022,
      "answer": "Gray",
      "question": "Dominant coat color of the Lipizzan breed",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 102,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    }

  ]
}`;
